jamiroquai.com 2018-12-27

# Jamiroquai Official Website / FOR MORE NEWS FOLLOW US ON INSTAGRAM @JAMIROQUAIHQ

  1. This Privacy Policy sets out how we will treat any personal information which you provide to us while using the site at www.jamiroquai.com (“Site”) or any of the information contained within the Site (“Content”) or otherwise during the provision of information and/or services via the Site (“Services”). You are deemed to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy on your first visit to the Site. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and such changes shall be effective from the date and time the revised Privacy Policy is posted on the Site. The Site and the Content, are owned and/or controlled by Jamiroquai Limited, a company registered in England with its registered office at 78 Mill Lane, London, United Kingdom NW6 1JZ (“Jamiroquai”, “us” or “we”).
  2. To provide the Services, it may be necessary for us to hold and process certain personal information. We take reasonable care in keeping any and all such information secure and preventing any unauthorized access or unlawful use of it. All personal information is processed by us in accordance with applicable data protection legislation.
  3. From time to time, we may collect or ask you to provide certain personal data (e.g. name, address, date of birth, gender, email addresses and/or other personal information relevant to your activities on the Site). This information will be stored together with any additional information you may provide to us from time to time, and will be used to inform you about and provide you with the Services and any other services associated with them. We may also use such personal information to analyse use of the Site and the Content, and/or to keep you up-to-date with (or provide offers of) other products and services provided by Jamiroquai or our trusted partners which we think may be of interest to you.
  4. We will only keep your personal information for as long as is necessary. We may, from time to time, expand or reduce our business and this may involve the sale of certain divisions or the transfer of control of certain divisions to other parties. Data provided by users will, where relevant, be transferred and the new owner or new controlling party will, under the terms of this Privacy Policy, be permitted to use such data for the purposes for which it was supplied by you.
  5. We may use 'cookies' while you access the Site for various reasons, including without limitation to avoid the need to re-enter details on different occasions and/or to collect information to produce statistical reports on Site activity which allow us to tailor the Site to suit your interests. Examples of other reasons include: 

• enabling our service to recognize your device so that you don't have to give the same information to us several times;  
• recognizing that you may already have given a username and password so that you don't need to do it for every web page requested; and/or,  
• measuring how many people are using services, to make the services easier to use and to ensure sufficient capacity for quick delivery to your web browser.  

A “cookie” is a small amount of data sent from the server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Most web browsers are automatically set up to accept cookies, but you can set your browser to refuse cookies or ask your browser to show you where a cookie has been set up. Please note that certain features of the Site are only activated by the presence of a cookie and if you choose to refuse cookies these features may not be available to you. Some internet browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. These settings will typically be found in the 'options' or 'preferences' menu of your browser. In order to understand these settings, the following links may be helpful (otherwise you should use the 'Help' option in your browser for more details):

• Cookie settings in Internet Explorer   
• Cookie settings in Firefox  
• Cookie settings in Chrome  
• Cookie settings in Safari  

Please note that we do not recommend turning cookies off when using the Services as this will prevent you from using many aspects of the services and/or the Site. For further information about cookies and how to control their use, please visit the following third party educational resources: [www.allaboutcookies.org](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and [www.youronlinechoices.eu](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)

  6. We may use third party ad networks to manage any advertising that may appear on the Site and other sites from time to time. Such ad network partners may use cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on the Site and other sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. We may also use local “shared objects”, also known as “Flash” cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, see <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118>). If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising, and you will continue to receive generic ads.
  7. If you do not want us to retain or use your personal information in any way, please do not provide the data to us or, if you have already provided personal information and wish to withdraw your consent, please click here or you can contact us at [webmaster@jamiroquai.com](mailto:webmaster@jamiroquai.com) or by post at:

P.O. Box 68  
Princes Risborough  
Buckinghamshire  
HP27 9YT  
United Kingdom  

  8. If you have any queries about this Privacy Policy or wish to resume receiving information which you may have previously opted out of receiving, please click here or you can contact us at [webmaster@jamiroquai.com](mailto:webmaster@jamiroquai.com) or by post at:

P.O. Box 68  
Princes Risborough  
Buckinghamshire  
HP27 9YT  
United Kingdom
